A Finding Aid to the Ivan C. Karp Papers and OK Harris Works of Art Gallery Records, 1960-2014, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition Files, 1969-2014; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 1.2 Linear feet Boxes 3-4
  - Antique Exhibitions - "Vintage Board Games" (1993 May-July 16), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Special Event Exhibitions - "Art at the Armory" (1988 January 28-31), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Special Event Exhibitions - "Art against AIDS" (1987), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Special Event Exhibitions - "Vietnamese Propaganda Art" (1995 September 16-October 7), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Special Event Exhibitions - "I Love New York Benefit" (2001 October 17-November 3), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Special Event Exhibitions - "American Abstract Artists, 75th Anniversary Exhibition" (2011 November 3-27), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Summer Invitationals (1975-2007), 1974-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6-13)
  - Summer Invitationals - "Centennial Biennial Invitational" (1991 June 1-July 12), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Summer Invitationals - "The Big Picture" (1992 May 30-July 17), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Summer Invitationals - "Subject: Object" (2003 May 31-July 18 and 2003 September 2-September 6), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Summer Invitationals - "Illuminators" (2013 June 1-July 19 and 2013 September 3-September 7), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - "Letters from Artists Seeking an Exhibition at OK Harris" (circa 2008-circa 2012), circa 1980-circa 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18-21)
- Artist Files, 1967-2014; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 34 Linear feet Boxes 4-38, 80
  Artist files consist of business and personal correspondence, biographical information, checklists, contracts, receipts, printed material, photographs, slides and color transparencies in various combinations. The files document arrangements for exhibitions, loans, consignments, shipping, and miscellaneous transactions with OK Harris Works of Art. The most extensively documented artists are: John Baeder, Muriel Castanis, Don Celender, Ralph Goings, John Kacere, Richard McLean, Robert Rohm and John Salt. Files regarding Don Celender include many of his surveys that were exhibited at OK Harris. Ephemera from Celender exhibitions consists of three different boxes for "OK Harris Art Crackers" based on the traditional animal cracker box, and two Chinese take out cartons of "Art Dealers Fortune Cookies" and "Art Curators Fortune Cookies."
  This series retains the order and labeling used by the gallery. Artist files are identified as "Current" (active) or "Past" (no longer represented by OK Harris). Current files are categorized as "Group A," "Group B," and "Photographers." Past files are categorized as "Group A," "Group B," and "Group C." According to gallery staff, artists were grouped according to how quickly they could produce enough new work for a show. Some artists are included in both subseries; within each subseries, a few artists are found in more than one group. Over time, it appears that some artists' output changed and filing errors occurred.
  The series is arranged as 6 subseries.
  Missing Title
  4.1: Current, Group A, 1970-2014
  4.2: Current, Group B, 1970-2007
  4.3: Current, Photographers, 1983-2013
  4.4: Past, Group A, 1970-1979
  4.5: Past, Group B, 1967-1979
  4.6: Past, Group C, 1968-2012
  - Current, Group A, 1970-2014; 4.1; Archival Resource Key
    - Baeder, John, 1978-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22-27)
    - Baeder, John, 1978-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 5, Folder 1-15)
    - Baeder, John, Digital Photographs of Artworks and Digital Document, 2007-2012; Archival Resource Key; .014 Gigabytes 43 computer files. (Folder ER001)
      Includes digital photographs of diners, scans of artworks depicting diners, a word processing document titled, "Chapter 6 - The Final Chaper: Doing Archaeology," and digital photographs of the exhibit, "Pleasant Journeys and Good Eats Along the Way, A Retrospective Exhibition of Paintings by John Baeder," that took place between December 8, 2007, and March 9, 2008, at the Morris Museum of Art.
    - Brody-Lederman, Stephanie, 1992-2014; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 5, Folder 16-18)
    - Castanis, Muriel, 1973-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19-22)
    - Castanis, Muriel, 1973-2009; Archival Resource Key; Includes 6 electronic discs (CD) (Box 6, Folder 1-8)
    - Castanis, Muriel, Final Exhibition at the OK Harris Gallery, Digital Video Recording, 2007 November 27; Archival Resource Key; .002 Gigabytes 1 computer file. (Folder ER007)
      Includes a digital video recording of Castanis' final show at the OK Harris Gallery presented in slideshow format.
    - Castanis, Muriel, Scrapbook, Digital Video Recording, 2020 June 27; Archival Resource Key; .008 Gigabytes 1 computer file. (Folder ER006)
      Includes a digital video recording of Castanis' digitized scrapbook presented in slideshow format.
    - Castanis, Muriel, Sculptures, Digital Video Recordings, 2007 November 27; Archival Resource Key; .032 Gigabytes 8 computer files. (Folder ER005)
      Digital video recordings of Muriel Castanis' archive of scultpture-based artworks in slideshow format.
    - In Search of the Toy, Documentary, Digital Video Recording, 2007 March 5; Archival Resource Key; .399 Gigabytes 1 computer file. (Folder ER004)
      A digital video recording and documentary short titled, In Search of the Toy, produced by Great Jones Productions with a running time of 7 minutes and 38 seconds.
    - 'Aerial' Muriel in her Studio, Digital Video Recording, 2007 February 9; Archival Resource Key; .388 Gigabytes 1 computer file. (Folder ER003)
      Digital video recording of Muriel 'Aerial' Castanis in her New York City studio.
    - Celender, Don, 1970-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9-23)
    - Celender, Don, 1970-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1-21)
    - Celender, Don, 1986-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1-5)
    - Celender, Don - Exhibition Ephemera, 1986-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Chard, Daniel, 1981-2008; Archival Resource Key; includes 4 electronic discs (CD); 2 computer discs: 3.5" (Box 8, Folder 7-9)
    - Chard, Daniel, Digitized Artworks and Digital Documents, 2007 January 9-2008 June 12; Archival Resource Key; .037 Gigabytes 7 computer files. (Folder ER008)
    - Constantine, Greg, 1983-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
    - Constantine, Greg, Poetic Licenses, Digitized Artworks, 2012 April 16-2012 September 15; Archival Resource Key; .021 Gigabytes 23 computer files. (Folder ER009)
      Includes 23 digital photographs of Constantine's series, "Poetic Licenses."
    - Constantine, Greg, 1983-2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 9, Folder 1-5)
    - Constantine, Greg, Digitized Paintings and Drawings, 2007 July 8-2007 October 10; Archival Resource Key; .012 Gigabytes 14 computer files. (Folder ER010)
      Includes digitized scans of Constantine's nine anamorphic paintings and five drawings created in 2007.
    - Del Grosso, James, 1989-2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 11 electronic discs (CD) (Box 9, Folder 6-9)
    - Del Grosso, James, Digitized Artworks, 2004 November 1-2012 October 10; Archival Resource Key; .021 Gigabytes 22 computer files. (Folder ER011)
      Includes digitized artworks of Del Grosso's painting, including still lifes of fruits and vegetables, Hershey's Kisses, lighters, American currency, and flashlights.
    - Dudley, Randy, 1986-2014; Archival Resource Key; Includes 5 electronic discs (CD) (Box 9, Folder 10-14)
    - Dudley, Randy, Digital Photographs, 2006 May 16-2020 January 6; Archival Resource Key; 1.18 Gigabytes 28 computer files. (Folder ER012)
    - Dufresne, Leonard, 1980-2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes electronic disc (CD) (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
    - Fisher, Bill, 2002-2014; Archival Resource Key; Includes 10 electronic discs (CD) (Box 9, Folder 17-18)
    - Fisher, Bill, Digital Photographs and Documents, 2006-2019; Archival Resource Key; .440 Gigabytes 162 computer files. (Folder ER013)
      Includes digitized scans of Fisher's artworks, as well as two versions of his resume.
    - Fox, Stephen, 1989-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19-21)
    - Fox, Stephen, Digitized Scan of Artwork, 2009; Archival Resource Key; .003 Gigabytes 2 computer files. (Folder ER014)
      Includes a digitized scan of Fox's artwork, "Plume."
    - Gelfman, Marilynn, 1972-2014; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 9, Folder 22-23)
    - Gelfman, Marilynn, 1972-2014; Archival Resource Key; Includes 10 electronic discs (CD); oversized material housed in Box 80 (Box 10, Folder 1-5)
    - Gelfman, Marilynn, Digital Photographs of Sculptures, 2005-2013; Archival Resource Key; 1.61 Gigabytes 92 computer files. (Folder ER015)
    - Giese, David, 1990-2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes 10 electronic discs (CD). (Box 10, Folder 6-8)
    - Giese, David, "Look What I Did!" HGTV Episode Segment, Digital Video Recording, 2007 September 11; Archival Resource Key; .175 Gigabytes 1 computer file. (Folder ER016)
      Includes a digital video recording of a segment from HGTV's, "Look What I Did!" episode, featuring Giese's Italian-themed home.
    - Ginder, Robert, 1983-2014; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 10, Folder 9-11)
    - Goings, Ralph, 1970-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 12-20)
    - Goings, Ralph, 1970-2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD); oversized material housed in Box 80 (Box 11, Folder 1-11)
    - Gozu, Masao, 1984-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 11, Folder 12-17)
    - Harrison, Allen, 1985-2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 11, Folder 18-19)
    - Hughes, Manuel, 1995-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Jin Jo, Sook, 1990-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (DVD) (Box 12, Folder 1-6)
    - Johnson, Mary Ellen, 2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Kacere, John, 1971-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 8-18)
    - Kessler, David, 2006-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Lee, Daniel, 1995-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 20-23)
    - Lee, Daniel, 1995-2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 5 electronic discs (CD) (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
    - Long, Keith, 1978-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 3-5)
    - Lynds, Clyde, 1986-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 6-10)
    - Masaaki, Soto, 1983-2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 13, Folder 11-16)
    - Matthews, Ben, 2001-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 13, Folder 17-18)
    - McLean, Richard, 1970-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 19-21)
    - McLean, Richard, 1970-2014; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 14, Folder 1-9)
    - Mendenhall, Jack, 1976-2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 14, Folder 10-12)
    - Miller, Arthur K., 1997-2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes 5 electronic discs (CD) (Box 14, Folder 13-16)
    - Miretsky, David, 1999-2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes 8 electronic discs (CD) (Box 14, Folder 17-18)
    - Montgomery, Steven, 1996-2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes 8 electronic discs (CD) (Box 14, Folder 19-22)
    - Muller-Franken, Johannes, 1998-2009; Archival Resource Key; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
    - Nichols, William, 1979-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 15, Folder 3-8)
    - Penner, Rod, 1993-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Perkel, Gregory, 1995-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 15, Folder 10-13)
    - Pfannerstill, Thomas A., 1993-2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 15, Folder 14-15)
    - Richbourg, Lance, 1978-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 15, Folder 16-22)
    - Rohm, Robert, 1970-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 8 electronic discs (CD) (Box 16, Folder 1-10)
    - Saari, Peter, 1985-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 11-14)
    - Salt, John, 1970-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 15-22)
    - Salt, John, 1970-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 1-5)
    - Seguin, Jean-Pierre, 2009-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
    - Sparnaay, Tjalf, 1997-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 8-9)
    - Stefanic, Zarko, 1994-2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 17, Folder 10-11)
    - Stocker, Tom, 1994-2008; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 17, Folder 12-13)
    - Szeto, Keung, 1983-2009; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 17, Folder 14-22)
    - Van Patten, James, 1993-2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes 12 electronic discs (CD) (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
    - Van Vranken, Robert, 1990-2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 7 electronic idscs (CD) (Box 18, Folder 3-10)
    - Weis, Ron, 1992-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Wood-Ginder, Cara, 1999-2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 18, Folder 12-14)
    - Zago, Tino, 1981-2014; Archival Resource Key; Includes 6 electronic discs (CD) (Box 18, Folder 15-21)
    - Oversized Material - Group A, Marilynn Gelfman from Box 10, Folder 4, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 80)
    - Oversized Material - Group A, Ralph Goings from Box 11, Folder 10, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 80)
  - Current, Group B, 1967-2007; 4.2; Archival Resource Key
    - Anderson, Robert, 2001-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 22-23)
    - Averbuch, Ilan, 1985-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 24-25)
    - Bacher, Thomas, 1982-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
    - Barnes, Curt, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Bechtle, Robert, 1991-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Beltzig, Stefan, 1981-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
    - Cho, Y. J., 1985-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 8-13)
    - Cone, Davis, 1988-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 14-16)
    - Falsetta, Vincent, 1986-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 17-18)
    - Fawcett, John S., 1970-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 19-22)
    - Franke, Kevin, 1982-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 23-27)
    - German, Vladimir, 1985-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
    - Hanson, Duane, 1983-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 4-7)
    - Hsia, Yan, 1974-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 8-11)
    - Janson, Jonathan, 1985-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 12-13)
    - Kagan, Larry, 2000-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Kolibal, Stanislav, 1973-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 15-19)
    - Koutroulis, Aris, 1977-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 20-22)
    - Koutroulis, Aris, 1977-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - Kuwayama, Tadaaki, 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Lakeman, Oscar, circa 1984-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Lan, Li, 1997-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Lazarevic, Milo M., 1985-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 6-7)
    - Levi, Josef, 1983-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 8-9)
    - Levine, Marilyn, 1975-2004; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (DVD) (Box 21, Folder 10-12)
    - Maravell, Nicholas, 1989-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 13-14)
    - Menchiari, Roberto, 1989-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 15-16)
    - Morgan, Kenneth, 1978-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 17-19)
    - Nakagawa, Naoto, circa 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Nitka, Louis, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 21-23)
    - Norris, Bill, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Nowlin, Oliver B., circa 1986-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Okamoto, Rikuro, 1980-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
    - Opocensky, Pavel, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 4-6)
    - Pavia, Philip, 2005-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 7-8)
    - Quasius, Sharron, 1980-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 9-12)
    - Radetsky, Jack, circa 1979-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 13-15)
    - Richards, Joseph, 1989-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 16-17)
    - Rudich, Richard, 1984-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 18-19)
    - Sorce, Anthony, 1981-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Staller, Eric, 1974-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 21-24)
    - Wesselmann, Tom, 1986-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Wesselmann, Tom, 1986-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Wesselmann, Tom, 1986-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Wilkerson, Jerry, 1977-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 4-5)
  - Current, Photographers, 1983-2103; 4.3; Archival Resource Key
    - Abrahamson, Mark, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Adams, Shelby Lee, 1993-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Ahlgren, Steven, 1996-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Aller, Robert, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Aloma, Lilyan, 2003-2009; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Barker, Joan, 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Bartoloni, Gary, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Balboni, Margot, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Benton-Harris, John, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Blotnik, Elihu, 2007-2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Borowiec, Andrew, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Bramson, Stern, 1984-circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Brickman, David, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Bromburg, Roy, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Brunetti, Eric, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Burkins, Nathaniel, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Ceo, Gregory P., 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Chambers, Tom, 2001-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Chester, Mark, 1983-2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 23, Folder 24-25)
    - Ciardi, George, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Colmer, Roy, 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Cummer, Willson, 2009-2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 elelctronic discs (CD) (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Davis, Alan, 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Dayan, Eddie, 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Del Valle, Eduardo and Mirta Gomez, 1989-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Deschamps, Francois, 2013-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - De Vall, Sue, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Duda, Paul Lawrence, 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - English, Ron, 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Feldman, Gerald, 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Fentress, Sam, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Feresten, Timothy, 1993-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Fretz, Stephen, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Friedman, Sarah A., 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Fujimi, Michitaka, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Fuster, Sylvia G., 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Geffner, Greg, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Gerbault, Arthur, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Gianettino, Larry, 1996-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Goldfarb, Anders, 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Gordon, Richard, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Graves, Ken and Eva Lipman, 1991-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Greenburg, Paul, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Greer, A. Roy, 1993-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Gross, Steve and Susan Daley, 2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Hafford, Jessica, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Harnett, Matt, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Hassan, Shandor, 1994-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Herrador, Mauricio, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Hower, Bob, 1985-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Huggins, John, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Hughes, Kevin P., 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Hursley, Timothy, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Hyma, Jay, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Iceberg, Keith, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Imes, Birney, 1978-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Jones-Sylvester, Noel, 1993-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Kemezys, Algis, 1988-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 10-11)
    - Kennard, John, 1987-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Koch, Lewis, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Kontaxis, Yorgha, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 14-15)
    - Kwilecki, Paul, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Kurata, Seiji, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Kuzmanoff, Leon, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Lawton, Joseph, 2000-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Lee, Daniel, 1993-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 20-24)
    - Levy, Builder, 1996-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Liffin, Joan, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Lucas, John, 1993-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 27-31)
    - Marshall, Karen, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Massaia, Michael, 2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - May, Jeanette, 2010-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Miller, Richard, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Monroe, Peter, 1999-2005; Archival Resource Key; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Morowitz, David, 1989-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Murray, Matthew, 2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Myma, Peter, 2005-2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Nadle, Ken, 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Nakamura, Dai, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Navarra, Tova, 1985-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Nogumi, Mike, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 7)